http://www.hbanet.org/privacy-policy

Awards ACE Awards
Woman Of The Year 2020-2021 Woman of the Year Dr. Sandra J. Horning
1990 - 2000 Women of the Year
Honorable Mentor 2020-2021 Honorable Mentor Dr. Rod MacKenzie
Events Event List
2020 HBA Annual Conference - 17-19 November Annual Conference Home
2020 Sponsorship Opportunities
Building Better Business Connections (3BC)
Zurich-Zug
Mid-Atlantic Region Mainline Montco (PA)
Montgomery Corridor (MD)
Resources Leadership Competency Framework
Make Your Mark!
Podcasts
HBA Leadership Project for MLRC
Lunch with Laurie: Leadership Perspectives to Challenge Your Thinking
Reducing The Gender Pay Gap To Drive Success In The Healthcare Industry
Career Career Opportunities
Certificate Program for Business Partnering in Digital Innovation
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting the Healthcare Businesswomen’s Association’s website and reviewing our privacy statement. The Healthcare Businesswomen’s Association is committed to protecting the privacy of our Corporate Partners, members, event attendees  and other customers. Our privacy policy is clear: We will collect no personal information about you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide that information to us. HBA guards your privacy and appreciates your trust. Emails and web formsPersonally identifying information that you provide by emails or web forms will be used only for such purposes as are described at the point of collection (for example on a web form), such as to update your membership record, respond to your questions or comments. If you provide contact information, HBA staff or its contractors may contact you to clarify your comment or question, or to learn about your level of customer satisfaction with our services.
Any credit card information you provide for goods or services is secure and used only for your intended purpose.
Information collected and stored automaticallyDuring your visit as you browse through the website, read pages, or download information, we will automatically gather and store certain information about your visit but not about you. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store only the following information about the visit:
The Internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if a private Internet access account, or "aschool.edu" if connected from a university) and IP address from which access to our website is gained;
The type of browser and operating system used to access our site;
The date and time of access to our site;
The pages visited and for how long; and
The address of the website from which the initial visit to hbanet.org was launched, if any.
We use this information to help us make our site more useful to visitors and to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. The data that are collected are not connected to your personal information or identity.
Links to other sitesThis website contains links to other sites. The Healthcare Businesswomen’s Association is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites, which may be different from the privacy practices described in this policy.  We encourage you to become familiar with privacy practices of other sites you visit, including linked sites.
SecurityFor site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, the Healthcare Businesswomen’s Association uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information or otherwise cause damage.
Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this service are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and 18 U.S.C. Sec. 1001 and 1030. Information also may be used for authorized law enforcement investigations. Except for the above purposes, no other attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits.
RevisionsWe reserve the right to change or modify this privacy statement at any time. If we revise our privacy statement, we will post those changes on the homepage and other places so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use
Contact Us
Copyright © 2020 HBA. All rights reserved.
